Chunmei, let me ask you.
Here in the Li manor,
have you ever seen a boy?
A boy?
What boy?
Your master has married three wives.
Did any of them have a boy?
All three wives
died within a month of marrying him.
They didn't leave the master any heirs.
Miss Mengzhu was born to his first wife.
The master only has one daughter, Miss Mengzhu.
Then that boy must be a ghost!
These pieces of jewelry
were left by the previous three wives.
See if there are any you like, madam,
to wear during the wedding ceremony.
Look.
It seems like the She-devil
really wants to marry Master Li.
Master,
are you reluctant to let the She-devil marry?
Do you have feelings for her?
Give me a break.
Her?
She punches and kicks at the slightest thing.
Whoever marries her
would end up beaten black and blue.
With Master Li's frail body,
God help him.
I'm done for. I'm done for.
It's already 4:00.
There are only three hours left.
Who on earth is the killer?
You like this kingfisher hairpin, madam?
Third Madam wore this when she performed.
I heard her ex-husband gave it to her.
Third Madam had an ex-husband?
Two wives died in a row in the Li manor.
Prominent families in town
no longer dare to marry their daughters into the Li family.
Just when the master was feeling depressed,
he met Third Madam.
Why did you stop singing?
Our master still wants to listen.
My husband passed away.
A weak woman like me can't run this place.
So I have to close this stage.
I made you two come for nothing.
I'm truly sorry.
Are you the Prima Donna, Yumo?
Thank you for remembering me, sir.
From now on,
I will no longer sing opera.
In this world,
Yumo is no more.
Our master loves hearing Miss Yumo sing.
Could we invite you to stay at our manor for a while?
We hope you can cheer up soon.
The master happened to invite her to stay,
and Yumo naturally became Third Madam.
The case files state that
Third Madam died of an illness.
What illness?
Third Madam didn't get sick.
She was possessed.
Possessed?
Third Madam sang opera by the well
and got possessed.
Madam.
Can't we just sing in the courtyard?
Do we have to go to that well?
My husband...
No.
My ex-husband wrote this play on his deathbed.
Cinnabar Well.
It's about a resentful woman jumping into a well,
and being saved by a general.
So to rehearse this play,
we must be by a well.
But this well
is the Dragon-Locking Well!
Under the iron chains at the mouth of this well,
the Dragon King of the East Sea is tied up!
The Dragon King is in this well?
Perfect.
I'll invite him to sing with me.
Madam!
Why won't you listen to me?
Through the years,
amidst the busy world,
the ancient well still pours out its heart.
Cinnabar Well,
a love hard to forget,
a dream of following each other in life and death.
Madam.
There's nothing here.
Secrets lie within the Cinnabar Well,
its dark waters hold tales of the past.
Who has seen the well builders of yesteryear?
Lost shadows bind lonely souls.
Madam, you must be tired from singing.
Take a rest.
How did I sound this time?
You sang beautifully, Madam.
Truly a legendary actress and Prima Donna.
Beautiful and talented, simply peerless.
Why isn't the master back yet? It's so late.
We agreed
that after I finished singing Cinnabar Well,
we'd go to Cuixiang Restaurant for dinner.
I'll go check on the master.
You rest here for a bit.
Madam.
Madam!
Madam, what's wrong?
Somebody, help!
Somebody come quickly!
The Dragon King is here.
The Dragon King is here, Madam!
Madam!
Somebody!
Somebody help!
Ever since the Dragon King came that day,
Third Madam has been delirious.
May the Bodhisattva protect us.
Please let Madam get well soon.
Doctor,
what exactly is
wrong with Madam?
It doesn't seem like Madam is sick.
She's...
She's possessed.
Possessed?
Did she offend an evil spirit?
You're right.
The Dragon King fancies me.
He wants me to sing opera for him in the Underworld.
Dragon King?
What Dragon King?
Please wake up, Madam!
It's... It's the Dragon-Locking Well.
Madam disturbed the Dragon King in the well.
Yes, the Dragon King fancies Madam.
The Dragon King said I sing opera beautifully.
He said I sing opera beautifully.
Secrets lie within the Cinnabar Well.
Hidden deep within the well.
Madam, what's wrong?
Madam!
What's wrong?
Doctor, you have to save her!
Madam!
Here, Madam.
Poor Third Madam. When she was alive,
she loved the master deeply.
After her death,
as soon as night falls,
she comes back looking for the master.
Madam.
Master.
You're back.
Stay back!
Help!